const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "What country is the tradition of 'New Year's Eve ball drop' in Times Square a part of?",
    options: ["Canada", "United States", "United Kingdom", "Australia"],
    correctAnswer: "United States",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which popular drink is typically consumed during New Year's Eve celebrations?",
    options: ["Soda", "Wine", "Champagne", "Beer"],
    correctAnswer: "Champagne",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "In which city do people celebrate New Year's Eve with a famous fireworks display at the Sydney Harbour?",
    options: ["Melbourne", "Sydney", "Brisbane", "Perth"],
    correctAnswer: "Sydney",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which song is commonly sung at midnight on New Year's Eve?",
    options: [
      "Happy Birthday",
      "Auld Lang Syne",
      "Jingle Bells",
      "The Star-Spangled Banner",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Auld Lang Syne",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of these is a common New Year's Eve superstition?",
    options: [
      "Eating 12 grapes at midnight",
      "Jumping into a lake at midnight",
      "Burning a candle all night",
      "Throwing salt over your shoulder",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Eating 12 grapes at midnight",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What is the name of the giant clock in London that famously counts down to midnight on New Year's Eve?",
    options: [
      "Big Ben",
      "The Royal Clock",
      "Westminster Clock",
      "The London Tower",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Big Ben",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "What color of clothing is considered lucky in many Latin American countries on New Year's Eve?",
    options: ["Red", "Blue", "Green", "White"],
    correctAnswer: "Red",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which famous landmark is known for its New Year’s Eve fireworks display in Dubai?",
    options: [
      "The Burj Khalifa",
      "The Eiffel Tower",
      "The Sydney Opera House",
      "The Great Wall of China",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Burj Khalifa",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "In which year did the first New Year’s Eve ball drop in Times Square, New York?",
    options: ["1900", "1920", "1930", "1907"],
    correctAnswer: "1907",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the New Year’s resolution most commonly made by people?",
    options: ["Travel more", "Exercise more", "Save money", "Read more books"],
    correctAnswer: "Exercise more",
  },
];

export default questions;
